Threatened by a ruthless demon, humanity was on the brink of destruction.
All seemed lost until a lone mage stepped forward and took up the fight.
After his triumph, he was hailed as the Wizard King, and his story became legend.
When the Black Bulls hideout was attacked by the Eye of the Midnight Sun,
Gauche, Gordon, and Grey were aided by an unfamiliar ally.
I won't let anyone get away with hurting them.
These are my squad mates.
Mana Corkscrew!
With the help of Henry and his powerful magic,
these four Black Bulls managed to drive away Radies and his group of miscreants.
But...
How could we let this happen?
Whatever they stole from our hideout, they're long gone with it now.
Here it is.
Well done.
The enemy had run off with a magic stone from inside the base.
Throughout all this,
Mariliona's royal knights were infiltrating the Eye of the Midnight Sun's fortress.
And Raya the Disloyal, the last of the Third Eye, was on the move.
Apparently, we have a real tricky bunch on our hands.
Seeing as Licht isn't around.
This is gonna be a pain.
Guess I'll have to suck it up.
I'm so sorry.
Now, I'm so sorry.
Now I'm so sorry.
I'm so sorry.
频道互動
It's power! It's so intense!
Mercury magic. Silver bullets.
Silver blades.
Have a taste of this!
Silver shining regal spear!
He makes it look easy, almost like he's up against a bunch of novices.
I've never seen Ser Nozel looking this determined before.
He's amazing.
According to the information I've gathered, that spatial mage has a habit of venturing out of the fortress at the same time every day.
That time is now. We currently have our own spatial mage outside, casting a spatial jamming spell. That should prevent any other mages from entering the base.
Get ready, Licht. I'm coming after you. And I swear, I won't leave until I've eliminated you for good.
Cherry blossom magic! Raging magic! Cherry blossom storm of petals! Plus my beautiful illusion!
What the hell is this?!
I was an arrogant man, but I've cast all that aside, along with my luscious hair.
This noble sacrifice has allowed my already great magic to increase in potency, which means that the rest of you will have room to shine even more fully!
You've got a twisted idea of what modesty is!
Water creation magic! Sea dragon's water ball!
Copper magic! Red shining mage!
Ah!
Ben, was it? I meant to tell you, congrats on making the Royal Knights. You should be proud. Even though my team crushed you to pieces.
Real classy! Taking the time to brag in the middle of a fight like this. Besides, if I recall, it was you know who defeated us.
Who cares about the details?
I'm putting my all into this! As a member of the Crimson Lion Kings, I know what happens to magic knights who disappoint Captain Meraleona!
Lightning magic! Thunder fiend!
Oh man! This turned out to be a really fun place! Too bad Magna's not here.
Well, whatever. I'll just have double the fun and brag later!
Oh! Isn't that beautiful!
Ugh!
That's my Yuno! There may be a ton of them, but they're still whips! Piece of cake!
We should keep moving.
It's no use. The outcome's been decided.
Oh yeah? You giving up already?
We'll be reborn soon. And then, we'll assume our true forms.
Your true forms? But I don't understand.
Come to think of it, what are all these markings? There are more of them the deeper we go. How strange.
Hmm? You see something you know?
Listen.
Am I the only one who hears that?
You morons need to get some better traps! I can see right through them!
Whatever spell you throw at us, my anti-magic sword will slice it up!
Seriously, why are we here? We can fight too, you know! Don't you want to take a break soon?
Huh?
Whoa! There's two of me! Is Gray here?
How'd you manage to pull off a trick like that? Clone spell?
Don't be a jerk! You know I can't do magic!
Did I say you could duplicate yourself?
Hey! It's not like any choice it is!
So how do we find out which one is real? They've even copied the lack of magic.
What about you? Can you tell them apart?
Nope, sure can't.
You're of no use to me!
I'm the real Asta!
No, I'm the real Asta!
Whatever! You're obviously the fake one!
You're the fake one and you know it!
Stop yelling!
That's one solution.
What's wrong with you?! You could've killed me!
So this is the real one.
Huh?
You survived a trial by fire.
And I wouldn't have brought anyone who couldn't.
This lady's out of control!
You've got that right.
She's a real spitfire, isn't she?
Copy magic, Aqua Curtain.
Copy magic, healing light particles.
You, my dear, are downright scary.
Wait! I know you!
That's right. Call me Raya.
And the pretty lady can call me whatever she wants to.
Don't get too hung up on her looks. She's strong too.
Then who are you? Seems like you would be amusing to fight.
He's with the third eye. The Eye of the Midnight Sun's strongest fighters.
Oh?
Raya the disloyal. He can copy other people's magic abilities.
Now that you mention it, I do know who he is.
You forgot him?!
Hold on a second. He's got a lot of power. We're going toe-to-toe with him?
It's too bad that you're royalty. I was hoping you and I could go out for a drink sometime.
I'll tell you what. Why don't I send you to hell? And you can have a drink there.
Ooh, you really are scared. No thanks, though. I've already tasted hell, and I didn't care for it.
Copy magic, Dark Cloak Black Blade.
Hey.
Hey, that's Captain Yami's spell! You can't rip him off like that!
I hate to break it to you, but copying people's kinda my thing.
Hmph. If he's that easy to mimic, Yami's got a long way to go.
Shall we start? Just so you know, you won't be able to dodge this one so easily.
Check out the stance.
That's the Captain's two!
Copy magic, Dark Cloak Lightless Flash!
She burned up the spell with a punch?!
He's in trouble.
Nice impression, but Yami's had more power. Work on it.
Oh yeah? Then...
I'll show you what destruction looks like! Flame magic!
Kali-ro-prachium!
I'll burn this place down in honor of my foolish brother!
I'll show you what destruction looks like! Flame magic! Kali-ro-prachium!
Kali-ro-prachium!
She's moving so fast! Plus... those fiery fists are chock-full of condensed magic. It's a simple spell.
She's moving so fast.
Plus, those fiery fists are chock full of condensed magic.
It's a simple spell, but it's effective.
She's a greater warrior than any mage I've ever seen.
Blossom! She's not fighting him from a distance, she's getting right in his face!
That gives me an idea!
I bet I can learn a lot from how she handles herself in close combat!
Copy magic. Healing light particles.
He healed up again!
Fine! I'm joining the fight!
Unless you want to die, just stand back and watch.
I see. So this time you're the biggest thorn in my side.
However, I wouldn't get too cocky since you stole that power from us, Royal.
Copy magic. Light swords of conviction.
She can't possibly keep up at this speed.
What's next?
That was amazing! I don't even care that it set me on fire!
Her movements. They're practically superhuman.
Copy magic. Invisible seeker.
Jeez, talk about unoriginal. Whose spell did he just use?
I know that one. I think it was the former captain of the purple orcas.
Copy magic.
Awkward javelin!
She can change direction in mid-air.
Try again!
She reacts almost as quickly as Veto.
You can't escape!
Huh?
Copy magic?
James hit Culver's Whirr!
Huh?
The most powerful water magic we have!
How do you like it?
Copy magic?
Salamander spread!
Huh?
Your move!
Water is her weakness, and fire is her affinity, but she can burn through both of them? You're
getting on my nerves!
Come on! Is that all you've got?
What?
Oooo!
Ahhhh!
Invisible!
Ugh!
Ahhhh!
Uh!
Huh!
Next!
Copy magic!
Sticky salamander!
Uh!
Huh!
Next!
Copy magic!
Your turn's ice-flow!
I don't drop you!
Next!
She's relentless.
Mira Leona Vermilion.
She's as ferocious as the rumors say.
I've done a little research on her.
This beast of a woman spends 300 days a year living in the woods and plains.
She says it's because the capital's too stifling that she prefers wild game.
Because of all the time she's spent basking in the mana of the natural world,
word has it she's taken mana skin to the next level.
And judging by those animalistic movements, I'd be inclined to believe it.
This is the first I've seen of this riot guy and his copy magic.
But I feel like I've got a good idea of how it works.
It allows him to mimic a spell from its attribute.
And that means that he has every single attribute at his fingertips.
Which is only possible because of his astounding power.
Because of that, any spell copied from an average mage would be more potent than the original.
But there's one thing he can't do.
And that's cast a second attack from a different attribute while he's already got one working.
We saw that when he tried it before and lost his transparency.
Most mages wouldn't stand a chance against a cheating scumbag like him.
But this is her.
Whoa! She keeps getting cooler and cooler!
Isn't there any technique I can steal from this fight and use later? Anything!
Huh? You're such a pain! Let's see how you counter this!
What?
No.
That's my sword!
How did he do that? I didn't know he could copy anti-magic too.
All I need to do to steal someone's magic is touch their grimoire.
And when I was transformed, I managed to make contact with it.
Not bad, eh, Ligt?
Copy magic, huh? Great!
Well, I guess this is kind of fitting for somebody who's as empty as I am, right?
Actually, Raya, you're the kindest person I know.
Huh? What makes you say that?
You see people for who they are and you can always find the good in them.
I suppose that's why you have that magic.
It's because I like people?
You can't use it without first observing and understanding someone.
It means you're kind.
You thought I was kind, but you were wrong.
Not only am I disloyal, I'm a lazy, worthless liar.
But Ligt said so many wonderful things about me.
He was truly the kind one.
And when you people deceived him and killed him,
an unfathomable amount of anger and hate welled up inside of me.
Your time has come, you foul humans!
I'm going to slaughter every one of you!
So it was just for sure.
You can't copy anti-magic after all.
She thought it might be real and she still punched me without hesitation.
If I could use anti-magic, it would have destroyed that fist of hers.
And such intense mana.
This woman's incredible.
It's not just because she's royal.
This is a human strength we've never known.
Are you done playing around?
Now then.
She's gone beyond mana scape to control all the mana in the area.
It's time to end this!
Monozone.
Calidos Brachium Barrage!
What's wrong, Mr. Third Eye? Running out of spells?
Yeah, he's finished.
There's no time to use fast movement or recovery magic.
What can I do now?
I had no idea she'd mastered a Monozone attack.
With the Monozone ability,
the user is able to manipulate the mana in the surrounding area to suit his or her own purposes.
This means that any mana using techniques activated within that zone can be controlled as well.
Try another attack!
I dare you!
No!
Additionally, Monozone gives a massive boost to sensitivity and reaction speed.
Borrowing power from nearby mana, one can move freely through the air.
She's too good.
It's getting ridiculous.
We struggled so hard to beat the Third Eye and now look!
Captain Mary Leona, you're so strong!
If that's really your best, I'll punch you until you're a pile of ashes!
Now burn!
Well, I guess that's it for me.
Wind magic! Tornado fang times three!
Huh?
Sorry, but you can't defeat me.
You don't have what it takes.
Nice one, you know!
His magic came from behind them!
Could that be the ability they call Monozone?
Now that I think about it, he cast a spell inside another spell earlier, and Spirit Dive, he used Monozone to do it!
Yuno really is an outstanding magic night!
Do you hear that?
I heard it before, too.
A heartbeat?
The mana here feels so... familiar.
It is gone...
I don't need no money
I don't need no魔力はいらない
自力で挑んだミラクル起きること願い
微力ながら1ミリずつビリビリ切り込んでく
世界を巻き込んでく
My disability is my ability
逆にそれが俺のエネルギー
どうしても自らを見失って
嫌いになって負けそうになったら
Just cry out loud
傷つく音に
勝ち向かう勇気へと導いてく
Our treasure
うなぎらないのは
最後に there is love
かざしたちがい光が
にぎる
The Royal Knights, huh?
I might as well play with them a little longer
Black Clover, page 92
The Wizard King versus the Leader of the Eye of the Midnight Sun
Go on, Licht
Crush that Wizard King for good
ご視聴ありがとうございました